<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://feed.eikowagenknecht.com/lootscraper/gog</id>
  <title>Free GOG Games (PC)</title>
  <updated>2026-02-02T15:00:33.634Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>LootScraper</name>
    <email>lootscraper@eikowagenknecht.com</email>
    <uri>https://eikowagenknecht.com/</uri>
  </author>
  <link href="https://eikowagenknecht.com/lootscraper/" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://feed.eikowagenknecht.com/lootscraper_gog_game.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://eikowagenknecht.com/lootscraper/">LootScraper</generator>
<entry>
  <id>https://feed.eikowagenknecht.com/lootscraper/10128</id>
  <title>GOG (Game) - Alone in the Dark: The Trilogy 1+2+3</title>
  <updated>2026-02-02T15:00:33.634Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>LootScraper</name>
    <email>lootscraper@eikowagenknecht.com</email>
    <uri>https://eikowagenknecht.com/</uri>
  </author>
    <content type="xhtml"><div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><img src="https://images.gog-statics.com/e43eac1b72b1655fa566deaa772c299fac8e2a3cb4a571c83268da32f7260043_product_card_v2_logo_480x285.png" /><ul><li><b>Offer valid from:</b> 2026-02-02 15:00</li><p>About the game (<b>Alone in the Dark: The Trilogy 1+2+3</b>*):</p><ul><li><b>Release date:</b> 1995-12-31</li><li><b>Description:</b> A suspicious suicide. A chilling curse. A malevolent power. Finally, a wicked dark secret. This is Derceto, a legendary Louisiana mansion where, against your better judgment, you&#039;re drawn into a world of shadows to explore the darker side of Jeremy Hartwood&#039;s imagination.
Despite a paralyzing sense of personal danger, your quest for truth drives you to investigate the old house. But, you didn&#039;t know that, by entering Derceto, you&#039;ll be plunged into the daily nightmare that was Jeremy Hartwood&#039;s life. You weren&#039;t prepared for the torturous howls that resound from deep within its halls. You didn’t foresee the shadowy corridors that seemingly have no end. You couldn&#039;t anticipate the brooding, gloom-filled rooms, the pervasive weight of dread, the heavy sense of evil that gills the atmosphere and the very house itself.
Had you known, you might have refused this task. But alas, you accepted, and now you must make your way through this spine-tingling adventure alone... and in the dark.
The grand-daddy of survival horror genre
A memorable soundtrack, excellent voice acting, and a thrilling story will keep you hooked for hours
Inspired by H.P. Lovecraft&#039;s universe, where ancient evils of unimaginary power play with human lives
Includes Jack in the Dark bonus adventure</li></ul><p>* Any information about the offer is automatically grabbed and may in rare cases not match the correct game.</p></ul><p>Claim it now for free on <a href="https://www.gog.com/en/game/alone_in_the_dark_the_trilogy_123">GOG</a>.</p><p><small>Source: GOG, Seen first: 2026-02-02 15:00:33, Generated by <a href="https://github.com/eikowagenknecht/lootscraper">LootScraper</a></small></p></div></content>
  <link href="https://www.gog.com/en/game/alone_in_the_dark_the_trilogy_123"/>
  <published>2026-02-02T15:00:33.634Z</published>
</entry>
</feed>